gkboptical.com 2015-12-21

# Privacy Policy of Gkboptical.com | Buy Online Sunglasses | Eyeglasses | Contact Lens | Spectacle Frames

GKB Opticals respects the privacy and confidentiality of individuals  who visit our web site located at www.gkboptical.com. We maintain this  Privacy Policy to help you understand our commitment to safeguard the  privacy of the information you provide to us on this website. We pledge  to treat all information made available by you with the utmost care and  responsibility.

 **Collection of Personally Identifiable Information** :  We exclusively collect, store and process personal data without your  express permission in accordance with the standard, legally valid  regulations as far as is required and deemed necessary for fulfilling  the contractually agreed service obligations between [www.gkboptical.com](http://www.gkboptical.com/) and you, the customer. Please note that you can withdraw your consent in  writing at any time with future effect. We do use your contact  information to send you offers based on your previous orders and your  interests. ** **

 **Use of Demographic and Profile Data** : We use personal  information to provide the  services you request. To the extent we use  your personal information to market to you, we will provide you the  ability to opt-out of such uses. We use your personal information to  resolve disputes; troubleshoot problems; help promote a safe service;  collect fees owed; measure consumer interest in our products and  services, inform you about online and offline offers, products,  services, and updates; customize your experience; detect and protect us  against error, fraud and other criminal activity; enforce our terms and  conditions; and as otherwise described to you at the time of collection.

In our efforts to continually improve our product and service  offerings, we collect and analyze demographic and profile data about our  users' activity on our website. We identify and use your IP address to  help diagnose problems with our server, and to administer our website.  Your IP address is also used to help identify you and to gather broad  demographic information.

We will occasionally ask you to complete  optional online surveys. These surveys may ask you for contact  information and demographic information (like zip code, age, or income  level). We use this data to tailor your experience at our site,  providing you with content that we think you might be interested in--and  to display content according to your preferences.

 **Cookies**

A  "cookie" is a small piece of information stored by a Web server on a  Web browser so it can be later read back from that browser. Cookies are  useful for enabling the browser to remember information specific to a  given user. gkboptical.com places both permanent and temporary cookies  in your computer's hard drive. gkboptical.com's cookies do not contain  any of your personally identifiable information. ****

**Sharing of personal information** : We may share  personal information with our other corporate entities and affiliates  to: help detect and prevent identity theft, fraud and other potentially  illegal acts; correlate related or multiple accounts to prevent abuse of  our services; and to facilitate joint or co-branded services that you  request where such services are provided by more than one corporate  entity. Those entities and affiliates may not market to you as a result  of such sharing unless you explicitly opt-in.

We may disclose personal information if required to do so by law or  in the good faith belief that such disclosure is reasonably necessary to  respond to subpoenas, court orders, or other legal process. We may  disclose personal information to law enforcement offices, third party  rights owners, or others in the good faith belief that such disclosure  is reasonably necessary to: enforce our Terms or Privacy Policy; respond  to claims that an advertisement, posting or other content violates the  rights of a third party; or protect the rights, property or personal  safety of our users or the general public.  
gkboptical.com and its  affiliates will share some or all of your personal information with  another business entity should we (or our assets) plan to merge with, or  be acquired by that business entity. Should such a transaction occur,  that other business entity (or the new combined entity) will be required  to follow this privacy policy with respect to your personal  information.  
 ** **

 **Links to Other Site** s: Our site links to other  websites that may collect personally identifiable information about you.  gkb.com is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of  those linked websites. ****

**Security Precautions** : Our site has stringent  security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse, and alteration  of the information under our control. Whenever you change or access your  account information, we offer the use of a secure server. Once your  information is in our possession we adhere to strict security  guidelines, protecting it against unauthorized access. ****

**Choice/Opt-Out** : gkboptical.com provides all users  with the opportunity to opt-out of receiving non-essential (promotional,  marketing-related) communications from us on behalf of our partners,  and from us in general, after setting up an account. If you want to  remove your contact information from all gkboptical.com lists and  newsletters, please visit [www.gkboptical.com](http://www.gkboptical.com/)

 **Questions**? Questions regarding this statement should be directed to the following address: [cs@gkboptical.com](mailto:cs@gkboptical.com)

 **Advertisements on gkboptical.com** : We use third-party  advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our website. These  companies may use information (not including your name, address, email  address, or telephone number) about your visits to this and other  websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of  interest to you.  
 ** **

 **Changes to this Privacy Polic** y: On occasion  gkboptical.com may amend or change this Privacy Policy by updating or  revising this posting, with the revised terms taking effect as of the  date of its posting.
